Class of 1888 Records, 1870-1958, 1977-2001
Smith College Archives
Class of 1888 Records
1870-1958, 1977-2001
Smith College. Class of 1888.
RG 80 UUID:6285fdb6-46fd-4b91-809f-617c1bf3c28c
8 boxes (3.25 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, letters, class letters, class notes, scrapbook, publications, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1888.
The Class of 1888 was the tenth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1888 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1888. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, class letters, class notes, scrapbook, publications, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1888.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1888 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1888: Baccalaureate 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 1)
- Class of 1888: Class Letters 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 2)
- Class of 1888: Commencement 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 3)
- Class of 1888: Commencement Music 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 4)
- Class of 1888: Groups 1884-85, 1888, undated (Box 1439, Folder 5)
- Class of 1888: Ivy Day 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 6)
- Class of 1888: Junior Prom 1887 (Box 1439, Folder 7)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1903, 1908 1903, 1908 (Box 1439, Folder 8)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1913 1913 (Box 1439, Folder 9)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1923 1923 (Box 1439, Folder 10)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1928 1928 (Box 1439, Folder 11)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1933 1933 (Box 1439, Folder 12)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1938 1938 (Box 1439, Folder 13)
- Class of 1888: Reunions 1948, 1958 1948, 1958 (Box 1439, Folder 14)
- Class of 1888: Reunion Songs 1923, 1938 (Box 1439, Folder 15)
- Class of 1888: Senior Dramatics 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 16)
- Class of 1888: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 17)
- Class of 1888: Senior Parties 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 18)
- Class of 1888: Songs 1923, 1948 (Box 1439, Folder 19)
- Class of 1888: Sophomore Reception 1884 (Box 1439, Folder 20)
- Class of 1888: Class Supper 1888 (Box 1439, Folder 21)
- Class of 1888: Class Letters 1888-1907 (Box 1440)
- Class of 1888: Class Letters 1908-1934 (Box 1441)
- Class of 1888: Class Letters 1935-1953 (Box 1442)
- Class of 1888: Austin, Caroline Sprague (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 1)
- Class of 1888: Bailey, Florence Kate (Photographs) 1888 (Box 1443, Folder 2)
- Class of 1888: Barton, Minerva May (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 3)
- Class of 1888: Benson, Sarah Louise (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 4)
- Class of 1888: Blaisdell, Daisy Luana undated (Box 1443, Folder 5)
- Class of 1888: Boardman, Harriette Holland undated (Box 1443, Folder 6)
- Class of 1888: Bosworth, Susie Belle (Photographs, etc) 1934 (Box 1443, Folder 7)
- Class of 1888: Brooks, Lucy Bagg (Photographs, etc) 1886, undated (Box 1443, Folder 8)
- Class of 1888: Brown, Adelaide 1925, 1935, 1937-39, 1941 (Box 1443, Folder 9)
- Class of 1888: Brown, Adelaide (Scrapbook regarding honorary degree) 1939 (Box 1443, Folder 10)
- Class of 1888: Burrington, Grace Alice (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 11)
- Class of 1888: Carter, Anna Louise (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 12)
- Class of 1888: Chamberlain, Jennie (Photographs, etc) 1913, 1948, undated (Box 1443, Folder 13)
- Class of 1888: Chandler, Belle (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 14)
- Class of 1888: Chase, Mabelle (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 15)
- Class of 1888: Church, Cornelia Chapell (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 16)
- Class of 1888: Churchyard, Grace (Letters, etc) 1885, 1912, 1914, 1931, undated (Box 1443, Folder 17)
- Class of 1888: Churchyard, Grace (Publications) 1910-1913, undated (Box 1443, Folder 18)
- Class of 1888: Cobb, Mary Esther 1926, 1929, 1954, 1958, 1992, undated (Box 1443, Folder 19)
- Class of 1888: Cobb, Mary Esther 1992 (Box 1443, Folder 20)
- Class of 1888: Cobb, Mary Esther (Poems) 1992 (Box 1443, Folder 21)
- Class of 1888: De Vol, Mary Frances (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 22)
- Class of 1888: Dewey, Mary undated (Box 1443, Folder 23)
- Class of 1888: Du Bois, Lilian (Photographs, etc) 1911, undated (Box 1443, Folder 24)
- Class of 1888: Duguid, Harriet Eliza (Photographs) undated (Box 1443, Folder 25)
- Class of 1888: Dwight, Marion McGregor (Photographs, etc) 1888, undated (Box 1443, Folder 26)
- Class of 1888: Eaton, Isabel (Photographs, etc) 1913, undated (Box 1443, Folder 27)
- Class of 1888: Everett, Martha Elizabeth (Photographs, etc) 1884, 1887, 1908, 1921-24, 1928-29, 1933-35, 1943, 1948, undated (Box 1444, Folder 1)
- Class of 1888: French, Isabella (Photographs) 1886, undated (Box 1444, Folder 2)
- Class of 1888: Gardner, Anna Warren (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 3)
- Class of 1888: Gower, Katy Helen (Photographs) 1888, 1903 (Box 1444, Folder 4)
- Class of 1888: Guild, Lora Elsine (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 5)
- Class of 1888: Hall, Sarah Mabel 1870, 1884-85, 1927, 1939, undated (Box 1444, Folder 6)
- Class of 1888: Hardy, Fannie Pearson (Photographs, etc) 1888, 1893-94, 1902, 1904, 1908, 1911, 1914, 1924, 1939-40, 1947, 1949, 1953, 1977-78, 1983, undated (Box 1444, Folder 7)
- Class of 1888: Hawker, Annah Dora (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 8)
- Class of 1888: Husted, Louise Akerly (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 9)
- Class of 1888: Jameson, Caroline Cogswell (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 10)
- Class of 1888: Kellogg, Annie Prindle (Photographs, etc) 1888, undated (Box 1444, Folder 11)
- Class of 1888: Kelly, Jane Downes 1938, 1950 (Box 1444, Folder 12)
- Class of 1888: Kelly, Jane Downes (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 13)
- Class of 1888: Kennedy, Leila Mantha (Photographs) undated (Box 1444, Folder 14)
- Class of 1888: Leonard, Florence 1890 (Box 1445, Folder 1)
- Class of 1888: Lincoln, Helen Stoddard (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 2)
- Class of 1888: Lord, Mary Caroline (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 3)
- Class of 1888: Lyman, Frances Pease (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 4)
- Class of 1888: Mather, Lucy Olcott (Photographs) (Box 1445, Folder 5)
- Class of 1888: Nichols, May Louise (Photographs, etc) 1902, 1905, 1912, 1924, 1948 (Box 1445, Folder 6)
- Class of 1888: Packard, Grace Sophronia undated (Box 1445, Folder 7)
- Class of 1888: Parker, Lizzie S. (Letters) 1884, 1887-88, 1893, 2001, undated (Box 1445, Folder 8)
- Class of 1888: Parker, Lizzie Southgate (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 9)
- Class of 1888: Plack, Martha Elizabeth (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 10)
- Class of 1888: Raymer, Mary Balmer undated (Box 1445, Folder 11)
- Class of 1888: Robinson, Alice undated (Box 1445, Folder 12)
- Class of 1888: Schreuder, Anna Ellen (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 13)
- Class of 1888: Seelye, Harriet Chapin (Box 1445, Folder 14)
- Class of 1888: Shevelson, Rachel (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 15)
- Class of 1888: Skilton, Alice Thomas (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 16)
- Class of 1888: Sykes, Alice May undated (Box 1445, Folder 17)
- Class of 1888: Thompson, Mary Frances (Photographs, etc) 1888-89 (Box 1445, Folder 18)
- Class of 1888: Twitchell, Susie H. (Letters) 1886-87 (Box 1445, Folder 19)
- Class of 1888: Twitchell, Susie Helen (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 20)
- Class of 1888: Ventres, Adelaide Brainerd (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 21)
- Class of 1888: Weeks, Katharine Ellen (Photographs) 1884, undated (Box 1445, Folder 22)
- Class of 1888: Wentworth, Ellen Lang (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 23)
- Class of 1888: Whitney, Margaret Olive (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 24)
- Class of 1888: Wilcoxen, Jennie Sarah (Photographs) undated (Box 1445, Folder 25)
- Class of 1888: Willard, Mary Randall undated (Box 1445, Folder 26)
- Class of 1888: Woodruff, Mary Alvira 1907 (Box 1445, Folder 27)
- Class of 1888: Parker, Lizzie Southgate (Class notes, Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1446)